So I click Next, and it says Grow with Pi.
So I need to sign up or login.
So I choose to log in using my Google account, right?
And I choose this one.
Choose an account to continue to pi your personal AI.
And I wait.
So it says Google will allow pi your personal AI
to access these info.
Continue.
So, as you see, it says hi, I'm pi a few things first.
So what should pi call you?
I can enter my name, right?
I say nima.
And I am 18 years old or over.
So I just said that pi can be a suitable tool for kids.
But as you see, when we're registering,
it asks us to be 18 years old or older.
But the point is that, yeah, I said, when I said kids,
I meant parent, parent, parentally guided usage for kids.
So parents log in, parents sign up.
And then they hand it over to their kids
for their special use or whatever.
So I click continue.
And I am waiting.
And as you see, it says, first thing,
choose how I should sound.
So these are the voice overs.
These are the voices that we can predict, point to have.
So each one when you click, you'll get a different voice
talking, right?
I mean, you're supposed to.
OK, it's not working.
Whatever.
I click, I'll do it later.
first thing, choose up. So we're done.